Come to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Hearts and the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
In every arcane world
Can't eat this can't eat this
My bagel with avocado. It's not good for tickets. All right. Oh my gosh
Well, first of all, it's so close
I'm like far away from the camera. It is like right up my nose. Oh my god. Everyone. How are you?
True
Right back
Little tricks as per cans. Hey guys
Oh my gosh, it's so close, but I look pretty good good thing. I'm handsome or else it'd be too close. Hi
Hi, hey, come on, babe. Yeah, I'm here
Where's everyone I see like there's like five people no one's in hi
Come on, babe
Why have hate watchers? Oh my god. Yeah, baby, baby
I'm not gonna get up until someone says hi come on say hi, and I'll get up or else. I'm just gonna leave
No, anyone say hi
I'm crying. I'm crying just like Brunford said
He's right. I cry all the time
Hey, baby, come on, what are you doing? I'll get up. I'll get up. Oh, okay, baby
Calm down.
Oh please, his butthole's gonna look really big.
Oh please don't show your butthole.
Please, please don't, oh.
Yep, hey watchers.
Hey watchers.
What am I gonna do with hey watchers, yeah.
I keep the green from the, oh my God.
Hi baby, oh I love you, I love you.
You're cutest.
Oh, it's so cute.
Oh, you're so cutest.
Where's your cootie?
Look at it.
My camera's like zooming in on its own now.
I don't know what's going on.
This is weird.
Oh, oh, you're hypnotized.
A hypnotized kitty cat?
The hypnotized cat?
Hi, babe.
Look the camera's zooming in on you on its own. Oh, what's up?
Yes
My god, oh
Look at it. Oh my gosh, don't get too close to the camera. Don't you go to the camera, baby, baby
I need to play another song I guess to
Wait for people hold on cuz no one's
Alright, bye-bye.
It's easy to just put the blame on me.
Tell me how I'm supposed to act when you all just won't see.
I was on last night home
Darrell
Darrell is fucking drunk
You're gay. It's okay. I'm okay too when I'm date
I need a date. I'm really desperate for them
anybody
I'm just kidding. I'm really interested
Wow, I don't know why it's like getting so close recently, but
I can tell you're gay you don't have to tell me that
Figured it out. I'm straight. I was gay until I saw this guy named him auto
Squirt lotion all over his chest and rub it in what kind of turn me off a man forever
But I
Don't know you like the glasses. Thank you so much. Well go out of loop a guacamole. I just had guacamole
I just had a fucking avocado toast a
Piece of guacamole left
Mm-hmm
Hey Alex started running he I mean
Alex were you playing on the stream yard that he did like five lives?
There's zero sound on any of them. There's no video
He got the
Some of the graphics up that was pretty good. Thank you
Thank you very much
Hey Guadalupe. Yeah. Oh Trixie Trixie Trixie, and there's Rudy too Rudy Tuesday
Yeah, I finished my avocado toast and I have like what do I have left?
I don't have any cigars left or yeah, I might and I finished my coffee. Oh, I have a little bit left
Okay, so I have a good trick. I
Have an Einstein bagels on the app. They have like free coffee
Let me know if you have to order anything else, but you can get a free coffee
And then you can refill it as many times as you want
as long as I walk back there.
So just across the street.
Pre copy all day until 1.30 in the afternoon.
Pretty good.
It's already kind of, it's good copy.
Oh, excuse me, I'm so sorry.
It's pretty good copy too.
I'm sorry, I'm discussing.
It's pretty good copy.
It's like vanilla and then they have half and half.
Guadalupe is following you around
Love you don't go for that. Oh
Well, you're in the wrong place. You're in the wrong place. This is all about love here
Look, but look there's many hate watchers. I was at KK's earlier
I was just like trying to participate and have fun
Everyone's so mean not her but and there's some nice people that like Barry and this sage was cool to me
What are you doing here? Why are you here go away get out of here?
And I was like, I'm not supposed it's basically avocado mashed up on toast and on a bagel. It's pretty good. Oh
Yeah, we're talking to Guadalupe guacamole
Yeah, she got a notification or he she or he oh shit hey guacamole
I know my coffee's finished, but so I don't know how long I'll be here
I was but I was gonna tell the story, but so I went to KK and then she was like, oh, okay
I'm gonna play Sam and slip and then she started it
Instantly private it instantly it goes off. Oh fuck
That was when I see if they had the they're gonna recover the beta stuff and they didn't like like my 10 minutes
I got with VW before I got kickoff. She's a freak. Okay. She fit him right perfectly here. Welcome
Welcome we're a bunch of freaks around here
Yeah, but people are so written the Tommy James like oh and I was like well, I was like I only private videos cuz I got like 30 privacy
Warnings from AMC. Oh, yeah
And then I was just like not very friendly thought I was like fuck it and then I was like looking Alex was going live and I
Couldn't find yep
I guess I couldn't find any content. I mean there's like and he was naming like the lives after me I
Looked at the psyche awakened CV lives. There's like two of those with one upcoming that he
It's like five hours off of Alex
Let daddy show you how to use the fancy toy
I need to teach you how to drive before you just like jump in the car and like try to drive
It's getting weird
Okay, Alex don't bother my chat Alex stop it
I'm gonna spank you. No, I'm just kidding. Yeah, Alex. Take your meds. What it was. So, uh, hey Darrell. Hey
You know, I didn't know I didn't have to pare down my
My mods, you know, I had like 50 mods
I was like, I think that's too many because tta elector was telling me she's like I have five mods
And then I just say no more than that and I was like, okay, let me count
I was like, and I like don't even know half of them and most of them are only coming
I was like, what the fuck am I just drunk modding every then I thought Alex is a mod. I was like, oh my god
I'm saying
and so
Yeah, no psyche that bitch is weird three years following you right well
Alex she followed you into my chat, and so I gained a viewer leave her alone now
You little brat
Am I older than you Alex I'm 44 how old are you Alex? I want to know about a seniority
Whose channels older yours or McQueen well Alex's I think is like was born this morning
Alex like what inspired you Alex though? You're like nobody's on so I'll just go on but it's like you didn't know how to like
Work this up
I've never found I've never been to a channel where there's like
Shows, but there's like absolutely not there's no sound. There's no video. It's just like the stream yard
Like the streamer templates
You came with easy easy cameras on okay. You're not falling McQueen. He's adorable. Isn't he adorable?
He's like our little like pit bull. He's like the little channel
If you can like put up with him you can put up with anybody, right?
Yeah paranoid
Yeah, no one's following you around Alex come on
She came with the felon who's the felon I'm not a felon
Oh, are you
Because what happened when you fell in on the oh, okay? No come Alex don't thought please don't
Get in trouble. I would get in trouble for all the accusations you make Alex
I get oh Alex summer and beta and I shouldn't say the names, but it's like they're like
Well, Alex told me to suck a dick and it's like well
didn't tell you I didn't say that Alex did I mean I can't control his mouth have
you ever tried I mean he is a mod who's on the run now I don't know let me see
who's on the run a few people then anyway I'm I'm about to be on the run
allied continues to bother me but oh my gosh and oh and Alex was in KK's yeah
Alex, but then I wanted to see if they would show like the 10 minutes of like the cucked, you know
The content were beat and I everyone is he beat and I do a one-on-one and
Then it was like we're gonna do like over 10 minutes, but then at 10 minutes. He was a lot
I only got 10 minutes immunity
He just took his sweet ass time playing that
Meow meow meow. I don't know how this there's a meow song playing. I know we did
I'm not gonna say anything. I don't know anything about it. I don't know anything about it. I
Don't I don't know but you know that person does follow me on a tiktok not not the
No, not that person though
Yeah
Ah
You think like Q did something
Just kidding. I don't know anything about it. I really don't know I don't anything about it
So why is like one why are three people talking and there's 16 people in the chat?
Is this like all hate watching people who are who are these other people?
Identify yourselves immediately. I'm gonna do a strip search for everybody. There's 19 people now in the chat three people talking
This is disturbing. I
don't like
when there's
19 people in the chat and three people talking. Oh, oh, okay stargazer
Stargazer. Oh, there's Nick. Okay, four people talking. How are you stargazer? Are you?
Michelle
Because I have everyone blocked I
Just have like 50 of Allied Allied's counts blocked
I think that he's the only one I've ever blocked or the people that are just like
Really rude. Hey, there's time. Hey, what's up time?
Time is
On my side
Yes, it is. Okay
Did anybody see the hate streams the haters club streams?
Who is there time was there right now?
Alex was there Alex Alex had my back
Let's let's see Alex took over my chat. I would not type nothing until you asked me up. Oh
Why are you mad?
Alex now you're bothering people
It's okay, you don't have to type anything just just read just
Side I from you won't see you if you don't hey, what's up kind of what stuff? Oh kind of wait. She said I don't know
Well, I'm not like, or you're just talking like Alex, Alex, you do have my back, you know, it's kind of like, you know, like the police department, right?
It's like nobody likes cops really, but we need them, or else there's no order or anything.
And then cops are like the biggest assholes too, but we just need them because imagine if like we didn't have cops, like who would enforce the laws or anything.
need security. He's just basically a glorified mall security guard, and I'm a
mall kind of. Don't get mad at me. Like why don't I get mad at me? Oh, you know, you
should hear what he says to me. Exiled one. Hold on, let me think. Hold on. Exiled. Oh, you.
Exiled one. Hmm. You want the link?
No one's mad at me. Okay. Okay
just
You're saying oh, well, I saw Alex is here. So you've not one's talking. Okay, that's fine
Yeah, Alex is like he's like you just need I just need him here, you know
he like
Scares away some people. I don't he's
Don't know I want some smoke support. I want some smoke. Okay. Give me some smoke this morning. Okay. I'll fight with you
Get that exile wants to fight. I'm gonna fight with you
My baby. No, no, you can't smoke no smoke for you. No kitty can't scan smoke
Any hands do oh, okay, hold on any handsome door knockers
No, but there was really nice people the other day. There was really nice people
It was the saddest thing though. This guy can't I heard to him this guy with his granddaughter outside and like
He's like, okay, we can go to the park as soon as you know, we pick up the scrap metal and she's like grandpa
Grandpa why isn't he answering the door? He's gonna answer. He's gonna answer. It's just so sad
It was sad
Why waste a grandfather granddaughter's time like that's just
Doesn't think about the people he hurts besides me, right?
Yo
Okay, I'm sorry. Thank you because I want to have a mature conversation with you. It was
brought to our attention that you had some things to say yesterday. We're gonna go back
to not replying to this at least for a while, psyche. We're trying to resolve the issue
with you. But Alex is making a problem when he keeps coming over to the channel starting
and then the
Channel I get to run it like I want if you don't like Alex you don't like me you don't have to be here
Okay, no, I'm trying to give you a chance to resolve it
So your content just don't come become us constantly going back and forth and boring with chat out of your audience
I'll worry about the content. I don't need you producing the show. I just need you to have a conversation with me. Okay, so let's have a conversation
That's what I'm saying. I'm not trying to produce the show. I'm just saying over time people are gonna get bored with this
This is I don't care. I don't care if they do. I
What do I care? What is most of the audience done for me lately?
Except go on hate shows and like talk shit about me. So what what do I care?
You know, Alex is the only one that depended me out of anybody on the show. So yes
And if you watch the show the other day, we really didn't have much to say about you it up
Because you know show and it's like I mean how much is there going to be a positive individual
And you're the one putting out the negative energy first psyche. I am hey
I'm not trying to put out negative energy but you understand what you're doing those like I'm parted
With negativity. I am just fucking hate it and I'm a nice person
I'm like probably one of the nicest people in this whole panel
I'm like probably one of the kindest open-hearted like
Try to allow everybody and it's like and I get this shit talked about me
Oh, he is ticks and fleas and bed bugs and lice and is covered in shit
And it's like and everyone's laughing and allies sending middle scrap people to collect things and it's like oh, ho ho ho
And Alex is the one sending the scrap man and the pizza, right?
He is not. He is not. I know who it is, because I've heard him say it. He even admitted on that show. He admitted it. I have eclipsed.
And it's like, you know, so, like, whatever, I know.
I would always take an advantage.
Why would Alex do that? Why would Alex?
And we know who's doing it. Of course, we're going to use the advantage of it.
And we're going to take credit for it to get to you when that's the content that we're doing.
But it is actually Alex doing it.
sure it is sure it is okay yeah Alex you're in trouble your Alex is it your
jig is up Alex I'm not asking for you to put Alex in trouble I'm asking for us
to have a resolve if you go back and watch our show from last night we had
nothing to say about you psyche we move I had a look over there it was it was
boring as hell I mean I think you actually a little boy you didn't see the crowd in
And then you weren't talking about me. So I was like, I'm out of here. And I just like, Oh, so it's got to be talk about you to be exciting is what you're saying pretty much. Exactly. Exactly. Because it was just like boring. Anyway, I'm not going to try to put him down. He's fine. He's fine. Let him run his channel. It's more of a different kind of show than mine. I'm not going to put him down. I'm not going to like bother anybody. But let me just say.
It was more interesting when they're talking about me, but anyway, okay, let's go. Let's go on. Hey page. How are you sweetheart?
You're over all of it. Oh, come on page. I'm just playing come on
I'm gonna have you come to a resolve
We would be able to talk about you, but it wouldn't be in a negative way
It'd be more in a positive direction and you would still get promoted
Sure, it would be sure. I'm sure it would you have so many nice things to say. Yeah, everyone has
I said no, we don't but if we see different of course, we're gonna be positive energy
Also, we're playing the role of a mirror. What you do is kind of the match
This guy, okay, I'm getting a little bit sick. All right, I'm trying to be genuine with you
But if you want to continue
There's some clip or something from years ago of me on some other platform talking to some terror reader and I don't know anything about terror
Have you found that video yet?
No, but I am still going through the content and like I said
I would double back on J-Dog with the content that I said I had about J-Dog
And I did that, didn't I?
I want receipts. I'd like to get receipts when you make those allegations.
Alex, just stay down for a minute. Come on. Down down below.
Okay. Well, you can ask Amanda and Brian King has been around for years when I say
Something I always produce receipts. It might take a minute for receipts, but I always produce
Amanda knows about it
She she knows about me producing receipts when I speak about something. Yes
Well, you didn't and you made the allegation that's what I'm saying
It's like how about it's better to have the receipt and then make the allegation rather than oh
I think I have this someone maybe it was a different person. It's probably not even me
I mean, it's like I would never open to that
That's why I'm going through all the content trying to find it because I might come across it and be like oh fuck
It wasn't psyche
I'll leave that open air for that. That's why
We say he doesn't know shit about tarot and I've heard her repeat it other places and it's like it's just really offensive because
I do know shit about tarot. Okay. So well, I'm wrong
Then I when I go through all of it
I'll be able to come back and be like I'm wrong because I take accountability also psyche
Okay, you'll just know that I'm gonna be
I'm gonna be not happy about it because I didn't like that allegation and it's not I understand that especially if you know
I mistaked you for someone else. I understand it
But right now we are trying to leave the shit alone and you are supposed to be a
positive energy card read
I don't suppose to be anybody's expectation. Okay, I'm just gonna be me. I'm just gonna be
Don't I don't need to be loving like I can be like a fucking asshole tarot reader. I can be whoever I want
I'm in this panel verse. Is it all love and light here? No, I'm as much as loving light as it gets around here
Okay, just maybe you just dropped the whole tarot card thing because tarot card reading is to bring out a positive outcome
You should know this well, especially if you've been
My readings are yes, I do have a positive
I do have a more positive style of terrarium, but I'm not doing terrarium right now.
I'm talking to you about some serious allegations that were made against me on a show.
So I just want to talk about this.
Okay, so anyway, and I'm willing to talk to you.
I'm willing to talk to you and it's like, I'm willing to like...
Here what you have to say I'm here
Delegations about me, okay, because you know everyone there was like only doesn't know shit about terror
Oh, and now they're repeating on other places and so that's how rumors get started, okay?
And then
Positive about you I said that's one of the positive things about you
No matter if you're offended at somebody and have a problem with them. You're still open to having the conversation with them
And I'm having a conversation and I'm not trying like overpowering. I am the host so I am kind of allowed to but I'm trying to talk to you normally
But let me just say
That was that kind of stuff pisses me off
I like to have receipts when you're gonna talk about the stuff not to say I'm gonna find this
We're gonna find it the millions of hours of footage of late past
Yeah, it is a lot of footage to go through you know because I mean I have to go back at least two three years
And go through two years worth the kind
I don't know where this I mean it's just guys you see you see what I'm saying guys it's like
it's always the negativity that sticks and it's always like no one's gonna remember no one's gonna
care about your race I care about the receipts for the situation but nobody else does they just
wanted to hear me say you're really stupid and like I don't know shit okay and it's like so before
you make allegations
Have the have the evidence have like, you know, here I have a video to show everybody and here he is doesn't know shit about tarot
That's that's the way that themselves brought the situation up first
So therefore I had to go back
Afterwards and after I said something about what they said and now I'm going back trying to find that so
Hey, there's open air that I could be wrong
because that's two or three years ago.
It could be a guy that looked a lot like you,
sounds a lot like you.
I could come back and be like, you know what's right here?
I owe you an apology.
But until I get to the content,
we can't really have that conversation like you're saying.
So it was two or three years ago, it was not me
because I didn't have even have a webcam
nor go on any shows until about a year ago.
So if it's three then it's somebody else for 100% sure 100% I just got this webcam
I would have and I was not on any show or anything
I just started going like over a little over a year ago and I know
Tarot and I know I mean it's like I've been doing it since I was eight years old again
And so I wouldn't be like not knowing anything and like asking for advice from some I mean and I do support other terror readers, too
I mean, it's like I'm not trying to say this is like I'm not trying to disparage me, but it's just like
All that all that sticks is a negative. So be careful before making allegations. That's how I say next time
Have it ready before you make the allegation. Okay, that's all I have
And when I go through it and I finally find it it may actually even resolve you so it
You know, I can understand you being upset about what's already been said, but I am in the process
Solifying or disqualifying what has been said
Okay, but you can't find it that that that means oh it could be out there. Oh, it'll be it'll be found eventually
I'm married to the person that has the content
So it will be found eventually whether it is you or not
How will you know if it's not me if it's not me? What is it someone who looks like me? I guess
It very much could be I mean you're you're a fairly average looking dude just like me psyche
You're an average-looking dude
There's nothing wrong with being an average-looking guy, I mean they get a lot of chicks or do things in your case
Okay, I do have okay. I am hot. Okay. I am sexy
Okay, and I ain't nothing wrong with you. I've never you point about yourself guy. Well, this is ridiculous
This is just getting ridiculous guys now. He's calling me average looking. Okay, at least he didn't say I'm below average
I don't even know what you look like you look like you look like you know, but is that letter? It's like oh, oh
Wow, oh my gosh. Well, not you're not bad. You're not bad
Thank you. Thank you. Well, thank you. I appreciate that. It's pretty good
Not bad looking guy
I kind of picture you different looking different, you know, well, everybody does a lot of people think I'm a black man
because of my cadence I
Wouldn't do that, but okay. Okay. Okay. Well, anyway, I thought you were gonna look like, you know, remember, you know
Jimbo from the Simpsons. I thought you'd look kind of like him. Oh
That's kind of fucked up psyche
I just didn't know but you're better looking. You're nice. Yeah, like you have nice long hair. You're you're good looking guy you're kind of
Little bit like you smoked a lot of cigarettes, but you look good
Smoke a decent amount of cigarettes. I smoke more weed than cigarettes though. Okay. I don't I'm just I'm just playing with you
Okay, okay, okay guys. I don't I'm an ass. I'm a fucking ass. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
You're a good looking you're not average. We're both average looking men, okay?
I'm banter back and forth is kind of emotionally affecting you and I would think that you'd want resolve where we're not talking shit about you on your side
And I'm pretty sure brown bird wants resolve where your side isn't talking shit on our side
I mean we can play that game. I'm an internet troll. That's really good. I don't
I don't know enough about Bronsberg to talk to each other about him.
I thought he was a nice enough person, now he's all mad at me.
I have no idea why.
I don't have enough, I don't know enough to even say anything.
I was like, if anybody has a story about him, maybe give me a story and then I'll be able to talk.
I just don't know anything about him.
way of, you know, characterizing me and he sounds like he's pretty pissed off and I heard
he was like, you know, looked like that Albert or, you know, Bill Cosby, you know, with the
sinus infection.
But I don't know.
I don't know what he looks like.
I don't care.
It's like, I'm done.
I'm not going to worry about other people.
I mean, it's going to stay in my lane.
I'm on my own show.
Thank you for coming, by the way, and you're brave because, you know.
Nobody else nobody else over there. They're just like pointing it from like the other side and like you're actually over here talking
I appreciate that. I respect you for that. Okay. I respect you for coming one-on-one with me and you're here first person on the show
I like that. Okay
You're also
Reasonable, okay. I like that
Well, I can't say something about you yesterday.
I said, you handled our trolling well
when we came over from Money's live
and promoted his live in your live while you were live.
You handled that situation pretty well
and I gave you your props yesterday, Sightman.
I love Money420.
I've said I want to promote Money420.
It's like, you know, I hear you got like,
you know, up to 500 subscribers, good for him.
And it's like, and I also have him on my website,
Like him and he's a neutral person. I don't care for a lot of stuff people on a show
Everybody has built their shit
And if if we didn't have a problem with you your numbers would be currently going up way more often too because we'd be promoting you too
And we're not just promoting through YouTube for promoting through a possible platform
Okay, but I hate watchers, but I my numbers are fine. I'm not really worried about numbers
I got my as soon as I got monetized
the number is kind of like whatever it's like
then I can just have fun.
I'm concerned about the quality over quantity.
I don't want like thousands of haters.
I want like people that are actually interested in Tarot
and people that are cool.
Hey, we have Mason the drummer here.
Do you like Mason?
Does money's followers look like they're haters, does Bronzebirds or something?
There's a few people like that, who's that white guy that like boomy kisses that night?
Everybody's got a couple haters, I mean one of our main haters in our chat is Alex.
Oh my god, I'm so mad, I mean it's just like, most of my chat hates me, but it's like whatever, okay.
I'm willing to, I'm willing to...
I'm happy to help people. I'm a promoter. I'm a marketer. I'm also not competing with anybody. Yeah, what's up, Mason?
Sike, why did Natalie block me on Facebook though? What did I do?
I have, I don't know Mason, but you were kind of like kind of telling a little bit too much about, you know,
you kind of, I don't know, revealed too much or something and her husband, I don't know, I don't, I don't want to get into it, but Mason,
you have to be like more aware of like what you say on the air and stuff like that, okay?
Because well, yep, yep, it's like you
Come back again, okay. Thank you. Yeah. Yeah, how about say psyche right now?
We have moved on and we're leaving air for resolve and over time
Hopefully you'll see that and hopefully the dynamic between the channels will change
I'm gonna leave so you and Mason
Mason shut up for a second. I'm gonna leave so you and Mason can go ahead and take care of his issue
You have a good day. Thank you. You too. Okay. Thanks for coming on the show. I appreciate you. Okay. Hey Mason
Mason
Yeah, you know, you're saying a little bit
You there's some things that you just don't or you save for private conversation and stuff like that
And then you were telling a little bit too much
of your private stuff to everybody.
And it's like, I don't know if she,
after thinking about, I just don't know.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know why she did, but I'm sure she cares about you.
Hopefully she'll still be able to talk to you on the thing,
but maybe you were writing her too much or something.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on, but.
So like you what did I do that was wrong though? I don't remember doing anything wrong
I think remember you were you're just talking about like oh
You're talking about her husband and like stuff like that and kind of like you know telling kind of too much information
And I'm sorry, and that was maybe my fault for like kind of
You know like telling you hey Mason the chill on that and I don't know
I just don't know like remember you were a little bit
Just too honest
Skill that you need to learn called
white lies
White lies are when it's like you were trying to like not cause problems for people's marriages and stuff. Okay, so anyway
Mason I wasn't trying to cause any problems though. I know you're just very honest and it's like
You just told a little bit too much. Okay, but in my opinion, right? That's my
And it's like just be careful when you're talking about maybe it's up that people wanted to keep more
Private and stuff like it's almost private
Yeah, you know, it's just like I can't keep that stuff private
Well, it's about you know, kind of sexy stuff and stuff like that. Just just like you know, just make sure
You have a conversation like that you she knows what you're gonna say or something
I don't know. I think you may be told a little bit and kind of were through off guard, but I don't know for sure
I just that's just my opinion. Okay. I think that yeah, she does care about you
I think she was fine with you yesterday. You know when it happened
Huh, you know when she did that or she blocks you or what?
I was just no psyche. That was just yesterday that I found that out though that that happened
Well, it could have been way earlier or something.
I just want to figure out, like, because Natalie's a really kind of-
No, Saki. No, Saki, wasn't there any-
Remember-
It's like, it wasn't the time earlier than that. It just happened yesterday.
Okay, well, she didn't react too badly when you were saying it,
but I think maybe she thought about it or something like that.
And I just don't know if she wanted you to say all that, right?
It's like, I just want to make sure that-
Yeah.
You know, it's like you have to learn still and it's like, you know, and it's like, I know she, you know, you know
She she cares about you. I'm sure she'll probably talk to you online. You can ask ask her like I but really I don't know
I don't I don't I haven't talked to her in private about it. Okay, and I know
He's not he's not he's not there. He's he's very smart. He's very smart, but it's like there's no filter
That's the thing. There's like there's no filter and it's like
Um, you need like a little bit of a filter, especially when you're talking
You didn't do anything wrong and I don't think she's mad at you like about that, but I think that it's like
Maybe it was there was maybe a conversation she had. I'm not sure. Oh, I'm
See, I don't I really don't want to get involved in it. You see
Hopefully it'll all work out. I don't know what happened to me. Okay, Mason. You're a good guy. Okay
Yeah, okay, how's the house of chat, I'm sorry chat. Oh god, I
Don't want to upset him. I don't want to upset him. He's got to learn some of this stuff though
You know, it's like I don't want him to make mistakes and he doesn't get under
It's like a no filter. It's like you have to have a little bit of a filter
Especially when you're dealing with married people and stuff like that. I just
You're a little bit more
discreet, I
Don't know make sense. Oh here. Oh here. Here is Alex. Here's Alex
Alex
What am I gonna do when I pull you? Oh, hold on Alex
Hold on yeah
Is your microphone all the way up? I
Don't know is it?
Hi, it's my cock all the way up. It's quite high. I'm just gonna put it on adjust and so it's in the middle
Okay, okay
Can we leave it there?
Okay, that's perfect. It's fine with me, man
Good there you go. So Alice what made you start deciding to start streaming like you have your own channel now
And what's that? Oh my god, thank you. What a nightmare, bro
So last night of the other night, I was just like whatever let me try streaming
Because everybody's like whatever just like board whatever and it said you need 24 hour verification and it came in today
Like you're verified you can go live
so i went live tried to anyway yo that shit is a nightmare it was just me and it's a nightmare
i don't know how you do it bro that's it's a lot of work i can only imagine trying to like
regulate 60 people and and all the songs you do and all that shit bro just to get up on
I started just doing the stream yard until like way after I think did like three or four months of just doing
Just doing the you know, it's funny. I it came back to me cuz I a week ago
I was making fun of you guys like I can run 30 pounds on my eyes closed
You're familiar with the stream yard backstage for the guest and that's not too different than the hosting but you know
Yeah, we're getting the hang of it man here and there, but still it just to you know more and more and more
That's a lot
I would have liked to be and then you got all this shit the backgrounds and the psyche awakens
And then the songs like you are putting in time and effort and work bro. This shit is not just like
You know
Like I do it like just press a button on an iPad. It's it's more
But you know
narratively it is not the most mean it's like it's pretty user friendly because there's more difficult ways if you try to
If you try to do OBS. Oh forget it like oh for you wouldn't I can't even figure that shit out, right?
It's like I mean, it's like that's complicated. This is more user friendly. That's why I really like it
Speaking of when people are coming in man when you have fucking 10 people screaming and then the chat going crazy, and then
if you have people
Did you have people come in in?
Hi everybody in chat. I'm sorry. You didn't have people come in. Well, you have to put you know, but my advice is to put
I have one person with me like fucking I was just sitting there like testing shit out and having fun with it
And I'm like this is crazy. Like what the fuck? Yeah, well imagine like when people start and I wasn't gonna say a word until someone came up, you know
wants to smoke I was gonna have to play who wants to smoke panel but it
Comes to the panel and it's named psyche awakens TV and then they go into your panel and you're just silent
And there was no, no, so I started stealing names because I was up there and then I'm like, no one's gonna find this shit
So I'm like, let me put psyche awakens because somebody's gonna look up psyche and then they'll see me next to him and maybe come up
But no, you know, because there's it's a crazy hour. Anyway, it was like nine in the morning, bro
Like no one goes up at those times and then I started putting the people's podcast
I'm like, I'm just putting any name. I haven't put crazy shit like live news. Like I was just testing the waters man
you know you should put alex if you want people to come open panel you're right now i don't want
people to come i'd rather just come up here and have fun with you guys bro i'll leave that to you
man i'll leave that shit to you the master of any panel he's doing shit man you were having fun
and stuff but i was like i went and i like i didn't hear any
I saw I saw later on I'm like wow psyche did come like real quick
Yeah, I came I came after because you posted like a thousand times. She was going haywire. I just kept doing live after live
I'm trying to erase this shit. They're still up there. I'm like what the fuck is this shit?
It's a learning curve, and I will fuck that man
Okay, I'm gonna do like a class on like
How to do a stream your panel and stuff like that. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna write a good idea
People like you that like I didn't see I was thinking I'm like, I wish one of these sticks was up any of them just to like yo
Like, you know, show me the ropes
Crazy, I wasn't there for you like I tried to make the live, but I couldn't find that's okay, man
It's okay. It was the craziest. I went on earth. I thought he was sleeping with the fuck's up at night in the morning
I'm fucking trying to start a stream or at night in the morning for the first time in my life
Fuck that bro. I'm doing that boy
Hey, shan typing stream yard helps too
Yeah, if you type stream yard or open panel or like, you know, but you have to like at least I'll go live right now
I'll go live right now. You know
You have to have like, you know, and you have to the link. Did you have the link up and everything so people could join?
Yeah, I put the link I even figured all that out you copy it and it goes in the little clipboard and then you just put it on the thing and paste it
Yeah, I figured all the way
Well people probably over there and they're like well, there's nobody talking did you ever see the number go best past like zero on the
thing
I won't point
There's no sound or there's no nobody there
I mean, it's like how would they know to go up? Yeah, cuz I wasn't I wasn't making a sound that was my point
I wasn't gonna sit then talking to myself like a dig like money for 20. I was just testing it
I was just gonna leave my shit up there and see what happens and if anyone comes up then I'll engage
But I wasn't gonna shit. They're like, hey, they're like, oh, I'm here open panel. Fuck that. I just don't knew
that's it
private tutoring
it's
I see you
Me making a panel because that's exactly what I'm gonna do
Why do I keep on my I really yeah, I can see you he meant see man asked me to hide
for him and I did
She's like am I seeing
Okay, Alex hide me. Look he meant is saying it again. Why is he man saying that?
Here hold on Alex. Okay. Hey, man. I'm sorry. I keep
okay
Nick I what you were hidden. Why were you on it? Why are you hidden? I don't know why you're here
I mean because she asked for it
They can why you were talking a fucking ex out. He man was saying Alex hide me Alex hide me. So I hit her
the fuck
And now she's back and asking for it again Alex. Hide me. So why is she doing it?
That's what I think it is hi Alex I hide me so then she can come back to you and cry like Alex is hiding people if that's what it is
That's some snake shit
Okay, you don't ask to be hidden and then come back like Alex hit me
Everyone everyone just like that's a snake if that's her deal
Everyone if Alice is too loud just lower your own volume because he's halfway down
I mean, I can't like turn him down in world just turn all the way up
So I just do he she meant hid it not old ladies turn on his volume. What the fuck man. It's just regular
But the thing was like I talked to a lecture last night and lecture was like I have five mods and then I'm like and then
I don't need it. She said then I don't have more and I looked I had like 50 mods and it's like most of my
I don't know how you I think I was like pushing the buttons. I must have been accident. So I'm sorry. Okay, but um
You're good. You're a good mom and stuff. Okay. All good. Okay
They're kind of roots. I mean not KK wasn't rude, but it was like some of her chat
I mean, it's like, you know, of course I expected it
Like there's a lot of people that don't like me and stuff
But they were just being like, oh, they're like go away psyche and so I don't just kind of hurt my feelings
And that's like I'm I was a mile out here
And then like, you know, and the wakamoli thing the wakamoli bitch, bro
I want to do with that girl's you can have her up when I'm not here
But when I'm here, I want nothing to do with that fucking animal
I know for three years, bro, that bitch is a fucking pig from hell. You have no idea what that thing is
Trust me. You want nothing to do with that
What does she want her terror reading or something and then you scare her away?
No, it's a lie. She does not want to terror reading that bitch is the biggest snake
She'll get a tire reading and then fucking laughing your face and throw it at you. That bitch is hell, bro
You think I would do that. I love girls bring every girl up here
What? I don't know where
That bitch hasn't shown her face in fucking two years now. She pops up here. Look Alex fuck that
Alex let's go calm down. Okay. I
Don't want none to do that don't bitch bro. Sorry
Okay, well Alex, please don't call my viewers
Dumb bitches or anything. Please. Please. Can you just like if you're a mom if you're a mod in my check
Yeah, but I know her before she was your viewer, bro. I have
But this bitch has history with us there's a difference there
If a girl just came over to your view, I'm not gonna but when it's so somebody I've lived here from three years, bro
I know what it's
Supposed in the chat for a little bit. I want to talk to you in the from from here without you being erupting
Okay, we'll sit in the chat
Because I have to end the stream in any way in a minute cuz I'm gonna go get another coffee and some smoke but Alex
Pretend like I'm the host just pretend. Okay. I'm the host
And you're my mod, so it's not good for my mod
to be calling people bitches.
You have to like, unless you don't wanna be a mod,
you have to be a little bit nice.
I can't have my mods calling people bitches sluts whore.
I mean, it's just not a good look, okay?
If you don't want to be okay, Alex, I want you to be a month, but Alex hid he man you saw it and I hid it
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. He man and hey lumpkins he man. You weren't rich when you first came in well
It was an accident. Hey lumpkins
You were not modded when you entered yeah, well, you know sometimes wrenches
Fall off the follow up people's belts and stuff. I don't know what happened exactly. Okay. I'm under a lot of stress lately
Okay, I'm under a lot of stress
I
Have people knocking on my door looking for scrap metal. Okay. Yeah, I love you. Okay. You're really good
You're really good with like, you know doing the cash-tap. I really really like that. You're a good mug
I mean, so I had no problem Alex
Alex
You need to take a chill pill, okay? You need to take it just okay. I can't have you
Saying some of the things you're saying if you don't if you want to say what you want to say
You can't be a mod if you want to like
Get a little bit more professional you can be a mod and stuff, but you can't know no bitches no
Yeah, I don't know if I'm being clear
I love you. I love you. You're great. I mean, it's like how about and you're a member and so your your name is already like
You know a different color. Are you sure you want to be a mod because it's kind of responsibility
and you're like playing you play you you're kind of like you're kind of like
Just playing around and I just can't I need to have a professional show. I'm monetized Alex. I mean, it's like
Everyone's like are you insane psyche like
He doesn't know what I mean is like and I'm like, yes, I must be insane. I must be
Alex as a mod. I don't know I
Mean am I fucking insane
It was like wasn't it like just $20 just to have you on up on the panel again, and how did I give you a lot was I?
Am I was I really drunk?
What is wrong with me guys?
Where people are on the way. Okay. Thank you Tom
Thank you. Are they nice people or not?
More people on the way to my house. Oh
Well, you know what Tom? You know what Tom?
Who's oh here comes Guadalupe guacamole?
Yeah, thank you. Okay. That was good Alex. Good Alex. Good job. You got it Alex
That's why you're a man. That's why you're a man. You've got it before anybody you get it. You got it
Good job, Alex. Good job. That's what I like. Okay. Now. Let me check out Guadalupe. Hold on one second. It's okay
It's okay, but if you see people threatening to send people to my house
Can you just please hide them please please immediately?
I mean that was pretty good Alex. Hi psyche. Hi. You sound perfectly nice. I am. I'm sorry
I I really don't know either if I had known me coming into your chat to tell you I like those fly-ass glasses
It's gonna be so dramatic. Thank you. I got them. I'm sorry. I don't know. You're so cute. Look at your little avocado pit
Stu Leonard's the avocado girls. I
Apologize for him. I hope he on he banned me and Chad just for all that. He banned you in the chat. Yeah
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Alex.
I am. I I try to be. I don't
last I knew we were chill
together but I guess not now.
What happened to Barry
McConnor? Thanks burning joint.
The guy McHugh is super triggered
by an avocado. He must fear
strong women. You hid that
person for saying that out.
Alex. Oh.
I mean, see, there's some people, like the guy that said he's in a relationship with Alex, the best person should have been him, but you sound like the nicest person, and it's like he's, he's.
Thank you. That's why I usually lurk here. I like your.
Yeah.
You're cool.
Alex.
I apologize for whatever set him off, and I hope you abandon me and.
I'll go back to being cool in the chat. Maybe I'll pop up again soon. I don't want a trigger
I don't know if we're out of reading. If you're just in a reading, you know, I'll pull up the cards.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, okay. Let me get them out. Okay, so
I'll do like five cards for you. Okay, this morning. Okay.
So and well, how should I address you? What's it? Just avocado, chick or walk guacamole anything you like
Alex, this is like one of the nicest people I've talked to on in my chat and you're like you're
Saying horrible things about I mean, I don't get it
See, I'm capable of ignoring him, but he just Alex needs I trigger some men
I trigger weak men. I wish there was like
a way to like wrench that didn't work or something like that.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I mean, you fight like a wrench.
It just like had the wrench on it, but it's like, it didn't work.
I mean, he's a member. That's good. He became a member.
That's awesome. Okay. So I got one. Oh, well,
I even went to super chat to get you on to block me,
but that can't go through once you have a model block.
So Alex super, Alex. Now, now you're preventing super cats, Alex.
Alex
Don't get moderating with emotions Alex. Yeah, he's modeling a little bit of motion. Okay. Hey back to the cards in the chat
Guys my mods in the chat. Can you like?
You know
Talk to Alex a little bit to explain to I don't I didn't I got Alex had some sense
But then it's like after seeing him try to run his own stream
He's like, well, I didn't want to like, you know talk on this
The other mods were very kind asking him not to block and to unblock me, but they must not
Okay, okay, so let me see
Okay, well we do have like, okay, so we have like these
This is the nine of swords and so this is like a lot of like thoughts in the past have been keeping you up at night
Here we go. Here we go. Oh
the accuracy, the accuracy and but there's a new beginning for you but it's like not entirely clear
you like you know what this is going to be it's like you know but it's like telling you to take
the leap of faith take the step just a horizon there's a horizon out there right it's the fool
card and the fool card is like this like basically
a new journey and it's like it will require a leap of faith because you won't necessarily know
what will lead and it can lead to this um this is the seven of wands and it says trapped but who
is the monster and this is like you be on a defense oh there we go it's like you're being on a defense
and who is the the crowd or is it the frankenstein that didn't you know didn't ask to be you know
great in the first place but this like the crowd right and maybe this fight and having to fend off
will like lead to some kind of heartbreak or
You know, it's like his awareness. Yeah, yeah
Maybe there's people that you don't want to be fighting off or maybe like, you know
You'd feel like persecuted by some so there could be some heartbreak, but also
We have this five of wands and the five of wands is basically
It can be like a good-natured fight. It could be like a you know a competition like a sports thing
you know, healthy, healthy, rivalry, just a good rivalry, rivalry, but I want to get a few more for
you. I mean, I wouldn't, I usually leave it at five, but I'm going to do three more for you.
Okay, so we then we have, okay, the page of wands. So this says new ideas, new energy, limitless
potential and a free spirit. Okay. And so it's kind of scary cars. This is the, this is the horror
Underrated. Yeah. Yeah, this is like something new. This is like and it's like a new start and something that you're gonna be really
passionate about it too because it has to do with passions and
Inner fire energy and stuff like that in your spirit. Okay. What else? Oh ace of cups. Okay. Ace of cups is like
This this this thing handed to you basically by the divine or god or whatever you believe in something that will that will can
make you very happy because the the cups have to do with the motion and things like that and so it's
like you're being handed like a fresh cup of blood or you know power right and yeah so receiving
power from power and it's an ace aces can grow into like you know basically it can grow to the
10 of cups which makes this is like the ultimate happiness but this is the beginning of something
and it's like you're gonna be handed something
Because of this like, you know free spirit and it's like, you know, just willingness to trust the divine
I'm gonna say and the Joker the leap take the lead right take that leap of faith and what okay
And then we got the Queen of Swords. Okay Queen of Swords. This is like
Okay, so the Queen of Swords
It has been through some stuff and then she's eventually like, you know, she's cutting off the head
She's getting off his head. No, she's not cutting off this guy's head
But she's you know, he doesn't look very very happy
But it's just like able to cut out what doesn't serve her in her life
I don't think it's gonna be nice nice nice, but it's like just the ability to but it's also because you've been through some stuff
Maybe I don't know if it's like a divorce or like a
breakups or something like that, but it's like now you're able to decide what you want. This is like a lot of times, I don't know if we're safe, but
you know, but it's basically also gonna be an air sign. I'm not sure where your sign is, but um, this uh, this one says, um, an unbiased tale of independence and
tradition, okay?
See? Unbiased. That's me. McQueen. Yeah, you're unbiased. Unbiased and it's like also you're independent and it's like, so you don't...
You don't need like a man or whatever or you don't need to be in a relationship necessarily you
You're good on your own too, and it's like you and I think you've gained a lot of power from these fights
I mean and from having your heart broken and all this stuff something good's gonna be handed to you
That's gonna make you really happy and it's gonna give you new ideas, you know
This is such a great reading imagine if I come up today to squash this
and so I hope you like that and I did that was great and
Way too accurate
Right off the jump. I liked it. Thank you. Thank you, and I'm happy you came up and I
for Alice I'm gonna have a talk with him and
If you hide this person this wonderful guacamole woman again
You're gonna be in trouble Alex. Okay, or the next time maybe there's a panel and he comes up
I'll come up and we we can splash this we could talk it out. I don't okay. Yeah, I'm a big girl
Yeah, see I like I like you're saying like you were like this monster. It's like it's weird
I mean, it's like I was afraid that I didn't know what I was gonna see or hear and it was like this
nice is nice his voice and
Cool person nice. I don't yell. I don't porn bomb
Thank you
Avatar I love your I love your avatar. It's so cute. Thanks. So you're all you you have a great day, and I think you too
That was great. I'll be welcome anytime. Okay. Thanks. Okay. Love you. Thank you for coming up. You too. Have a great day. Bye
I
Like that. I like her
Psyche Alexander hid me and guacamole too. I know he man. I'm so sorry
Well, and Alex now I'm gonna mod guacamole and you know Alex you really don't need a wrench right now
I do love you Alex. You don't need to wear a wrench. Okay. You can pay me 50 bucks if you want to get it back
But I'm gonna mod. Oh, hey, what's that noble Castro? I'm on you. I'm gonna mod
I'm in a mod, guacamole girl.
Where is she?
Is she in him?
Does anybody see where guacamole girl?
Hey, there's Gotti, Louise Lemmon.
Hey, I'm sorry, I'm missing all these chats.
It's Allie Strawberry, Louise Lemmono.
It's guacamole Guadalupe.
Let me see.
Alex, you're fine, Alex.
But Alex, you're a member,
so you stand out more than anybody
because there's hardly any members anymore, so you're fine.
You'll stand out even more as a member.
Don't need to see. Yeah. Yeah, I took his wrench
but Alex
Look, come on. Don't hurt my heart mate. You hit a he-man. Come on, Alex
What are you doing? Okay? I made the right decision online. Oh my gosh. What a loopy. Can you type in the chat, please?
Oh my god, now I can't even find her you hit her. Well guacamole is gone
Okay, guys, I need to take care of this
Um, I need to go grab another coffee. Is it what time is it?
It's nine o'clock. Okay, so the store is gonna be open for cigars. Okay
Ignorance is bliss ask Christine about Lupe. I don't trust Christine's opinion anymore
Christine might be trust her because she said I was not a dumb person. She said I just played dumb
but
She's not
really in the mood to give me good advice anymore but let me see I have no
problem I apologize Christina she wouldn't accept my apology so oh okay so
let me look in the back chat and I'm gonna go grab cigars and maybe brief with
my coffee at the bagels to a shop let me see I just need to make sure I studio
YouTube I'm gonna on a high guard loop a
Maybe anybody else that he hit. Oh my gosh, what is he been doing this whole time? Oh my god. I need to go go through my list
Alex, I mean, I didn't know you was just
Playing around and I do love you Alex
You're better as a member. I think and guys if you're not a mod just become a member because
You'll stand out even more than a mod, you know, and then you don't have to worry about
Modding so let me just look at the settings
Okay, there it is community moderation. I'm gonna go out of loop a
Okay, guys, let me see. Okay, so
Black RG is hidden. I don't know if that's a good idea. Let me see cult of VR. I know I hid that person
Okay, so exiled one is fine. I'm gonna unhide him a
Lot of these people are gonna be mad. I mean, it's like, yeah, of course they're mad at me
They think I'm hiding these people
Let me see taunt. Okay. There's burdo. Yeah, she should be hidden
Let's see Kentucky fried chicken. Okay. My call. Yes. I know that is
Nick purrs
Exiled oh my god exiled you have enough
Fuckin at aliases
Let's see
Jacob Shabay. I mean, yeah, it's fine and be hidden. Yes Nina. Yeah, she should be hidden because she's brewed
Yeah, the HIV awakens there. Okay, BG is fine. I don't know why he's hidden. Okay
Tony the yag doctor that sounds fine. I like that name
Um, let's see Fred Alastair Spine being hidden. Oh, Joseph Johnson. No, he's fine. Unless he's allied. I don't think he is
That's the
Absolutely not Mike Hall, you know, it's gonna be you know who let's see
Exiled trace, okay
Joe, I think, isn't the Joe, is that Joe Shipley?
Okay, Black RG, I'm gonna unhide Black RG.
Come on, Alex.
Doug, he's fine being hidden.
Pumonchu, Lurida, Spanky, I don't know Spanky.
Isn't Spanky not a bad person?
I don't know.
I think Spanky's fine, I'm not sure.
I don't know, I'll give him another chance.
Jesus Christ is hidden!
You know, hi Jesus
Smelly's fine, too. It's just Kate. Come on
Muffin top, I mean, I don't know a lot of exiled quadruple. I mean how many
Times has he been hidden? Well, there's uncomfortable. I mean, it's like, you know, you can let her talk
You let some people talk Alex. Have you been hiding all these people?
KZ's fine. Okay. I think that's that thing. That's it. I mean look at them one more time
Why pink boy birdo is fine being hidden?
Okay into the dragon spirit. I just don't know some of these people Joe 2.0. I
Don't see Guadalupe anywhere in here west coast, right? I didn't see Guadalupe. So it's I think she's unhidden
hopefully
Did anybody see if she got unhidden? I'm sorry. Oh
There she is. I got it. Guadalupe guacamole. Okay
Wow Alex, who knows if these are people that no wonder it's been quiet in my chat
Alex black or RG. That's fine. I mean come on. I don't hit him
KZ's fine being hit actually no KZ. I'm trying to negotiate KZ to
To to get back on the panel, but he can't do it if he's hidden. I mean come on. Maybe I hit him though
BG again, okay, I mean Jesus
Alex
Okay, is that what's mad about it? I don't know if that's a real gymnik, but I'm just gonna I don't know
I think there's a lot of fake gymniks, okay?
Big red. I just don't know some of these people. I don't want to unhide everybody
Yeah, guys, please Rodimus Prime seed mad. I think I hid him on purpose
Well dimmest I'm all on high them because so many people say oh I got hit and I don't remember hit it stay turn to spine come on
the spine
My god Daniel playing view. Is he okay? I don't know. I don't think all these people joe
I'm gonna hide yes Mina, too. I mean now. This is just turning into a mess. So I don't know who to hide
Gosh
Think that's enough. I think white rogue guy. I don't know
Kentucky cried frickin I
Mean burdo's fine. You can just talk in the chat. I don't care. Oh, I
Mean, she saw us my person. I really want to hide is like, you know, you know who? I
Don't I don't think he has all these alts. I mean Ziggy is hidden
Why are you hiding all these people?
No, I X
Okay, I just unhid like 35 people
Swagura Matisuki human I just don't know
Okay, I think I think that's enough
But Alex what if these are people that wonder reading and so okay, you're fine. You're fine
Alex
Wonder people hate me. They think I'm a hiding. I didn't hide all those people
Let me look at the chat
Hey, Sam
He's got like 50 sock accounts. Yeah
Think Alice got hit him when you took his wrench. Oh
Hey the loser Jesus gonna make it storm just over you wherever you go after getting banned
What do you mean the loser?
You like being mod you can't get banned I know I
Know some people do get offended right and it's like and I didn't do anything. I'm hiding everybody
I really don't hide anybody except yeah, yeah, doctor. You know, you know who?
No battery. You're cool
Just clear the list. I'm not clearing a list because there's a lot of people that I did have to ban because a lot of people were saying horrible things and I
But I will have to do a mess on the band probably soon. Did I save it? Yeah, I did save it
Okay
No wonder I guys I came in I was like there's like 30 people in the chat and like nobody was talking in that
They probably thought they were talking and stuff, okay
well
Well guys
That's that
Okay, I mean Casey and I are negotiating his return on but he wants that's why he kept asking to go on the panel because
He was blocked
Assie. Oh my god. What I mean. Can you guys my call is my call not a song. I know he's Tony the yag
Uh-huh hey loser a nurse is bliss
And I didn't mean to like, you know, unmod a few people and stuff.
Don't take it personal.
Just if you want to get noticed, become a member.
Because look, I'm going to restart, I'm going to refresh.
And then it's like, then I'll see Alex will be a member.
I'll see, you know, he'll be a good member.
How long have I been talking to myself? I've been sitting here like talking to myself for like 20 minutes. Okay guys
Okay guys, I
Pleared a lot of people off a lot of people. There's only like 43 people on the list now
Okay, most of them have names that I do not like I
Unhid probably 60 people
I'm sorry, I looked up and there was like,
I wasn't on camera.
You thought I left or something?
No, I didn't leave, I was just,
oh, look at my face, it's all red.
Oh my God, this is bad.
It's all red.
Lupe just got here and got a wrench?
Yeah, because Lupe is, I've talked to Lupe on the screen,
I've talked to you two, Smash,
but Smash is like, weren't you like,
Saying mean things to me before you and also I don't really need that many mods
So if you want to get noticed and stuff like that and not get probably hidden less like you're really bad
Just get a membership
It's five bucks and then you know
You'll stand out in the chat. I'll shout out. I'll shout out all the members
Yeah, I'm gonna shout out all the members in the chat right now. Well, Alex is the only member and he's hidden right now
the fuck
any members there's a one not one member not one member what a sad state of affairs
what a sad state of affairs oh shan camp thank you shan shan is a member thank you
shout out to shan special shout out my bud thank you shan that's it one person
one member
kind of sad. One number. Okay guys, I'll be back later. Thank you for the advice and stuff.
Do you want to see a video before you go? Let me see.
Here's a video for you guys enjoy. I'll see you soon
I've been missing in my sleep